Railroad Case Files 5014
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Railroad Case Files
1910-1965
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives
5014
17 cubic feet
17 linear ft.
Records (documents), case files.
This collection consists of the case files of arbitrations, mediations, and disputes between rail carriers and their employees' labor unions in front of various government boards.
8192586
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, April 15, 2013
EAD encoding:
Elizabeth Parker, March 19, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Railroads; Railroads -- Employees -- Labor unions; United States Railroad Labor Board; Eastern, Western and Southeastern Carriers; United States. National Mediation Board; Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen; Order of Railway Conductors of America; Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen; Order of Railroad Telegraphers (U.S.)
8192586
- Arbitration Proceedings in the Matter of the Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railroad, et al and the Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, Chicago, May l6-June 3, 1910. Volumes 1 and 3.. (Box 1)
  - Proceedings of the United States Railroad Labor Board Docket No. 4055 Volume VII, 1924 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    Atchison, Topeka & Santa Fe Railway v. Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen
  - Proceedings of the United States Railroad Labor Board Docket No. 4055 Volume VI, 1924 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Proceedings of the United States Railroad Labor Board Docket No. 4055 Volume No. 4, 1924 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Proceedings of the United States Railroad Labor Board Docket No. 4055 Volume No. 3, 1924 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Proceedings of the United States Railroad Labor Board Docket No. 4055 Volume No. 2, 1924 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Firemen's Arbitration Volume III, 1910 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Arbitration proceedings in the matter of the Atchison, Topeka & Santa Fe Railway et al. and the Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen. Chicago, May 16 to June 3, 1910.
  - Firemen's Arbitration Volume 1, 1910 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Arbitration Proceedings in the Matter of the Achison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railroad, et al and the Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, Chicago, May l6-June 3, 1910. Volumes 1 and 3.. (Box 2)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume No. 9, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Appointed by the President of the United States to investigate and report certain differences between the Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, et al., and Atchison, Topeka & Santa Fe Railway, et al.
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume No. 1, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume No. 2, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume No. 3, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume No. 5, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume No. 6, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume No. 7, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume No. 8, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume No. 10, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume No. 12, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume No. 13, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume No. 14, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume No. 15, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume No. 16, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume No. 17, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume No. 18, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume No. 19, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume No. 20, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume No. 11, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Arbitration Proceedings in the Matter of the Achison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railroad, et al and the Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, Chicago, May l6-June 3, 1910. Volumes 1 and 3.. (Box 3)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume No. 31, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume No. 22, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume No. 23, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume No. 24, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume No. 25, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume No. 26, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume No. 27, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume No. 21, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume No. 30, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume No. 28, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume No. 29, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume No. Appendix, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume No. 32, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Eastern, Western and Southeastern Carriers' Committees and Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, Volume 2, 1953 (Box 3.1, Folder 1)
  October 28, 1953
- Eastern, Western and Southeastern Carriers' Committees and Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, Volume 3, 1953 (Box 3.1, Folder 2)
  October 29, 1953
- Eastern, Western and Southeastern Carriers' Committees and Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, Volume 4, 1953 (Box 3.1, Folder 3)
  October 30, 1953
- Eastern, Western and Southeastern Carriers' Committees and Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, Volume 26, 1954 (Box 3.1, Folder 4)
  March 15, 1954
- Eastern, Western and Southeastern Carriers' Committees and Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, Volume 24, 1954 (Box 3.1, Folder 5)
  January 15, 1954
- Eastern, Western and Southeastern Carriers' Committees and Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, Volume 23, 1954 (Box 3.1, Folder 6)
  January 14, 1954
- Eastern, Western and Southeastern Carriers' Committees and Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, Volume 20, 1954 (Box 3.1, Folder 7)
  January 11, 1954
- Eastern, Western and Southeastern Carriers' Committees and Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, Volume 21, 1954 (Box 3.1, Folder 8)
  January 12, 1954
- Eastern, Western and Southeastern Carriers' Committees and Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, Volume 22, 1954 (Box 3.1, Folder 9)
  January 13, 1954
- Eastern, Western and Southeastern Carriers' Committees and Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, Volume 15, 1953 (Box 3.1, Folder 10)
  November 30, 1953
- Eastern, Western and Southeastern Carriers' Committees and Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, Volume 16, 1953 (Box 3.1, Folder 11)
  December 1, 1953
- Eastern, Western and Southeastern Carriers' Committees and Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, Volume 16, 1953 (Box 3.1, Folder 12)
- Eastern, Western and Southeastern Carriers' Committees and Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, Volume 17, 1953 (Box 3.1, Folder 13)
  December 2, 1953
- Eastern, Western and Southeastern Carriers' Committees and Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, Volume 19, 1953 (Box 3.1, Folder 14)
  December 4, 1953
- Eastern, Western and Southeastern Carriers' Committees and Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, Volume 10, 1953 (Box 3.1, Folder 15)
  November 16, 1953
- Eastern, Western and Southeastern Carriers' Committees and Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, Volume 11, 1953 (Box 3.1, Folder 16)
  November 17, 1953
- Eastern, Western and Southeastern Carriers' Committees and Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, Volume 12, 1953 (Box 3.1, Folder 17)
  November 18, 1953
- Eastern, Western and Southeastern Carriers' Committees and Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, Volume 13, 1953 (Box 3.1, Folder 18)
  November 19, 1953
- Eastern, Western and Southeastern Carriers' Committees and Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, Volume 14, 1953 (Box 3.1, Folder 19)
  November 20, 1953
- Eastern, Western and Southeastern Carriers' Committees and Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, Volume 6, 1953 (Box 3.1, Folder 20)
  November 10, 1953
- Eastern, Western and Southeastern Carriers' Committees and Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, Volume 7, 1953 (Box 3.1, Folder 21)
  November 11, 1953
- Eastern, Western and Southeastern Carriers' Committees and Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, Volume 8, 1953 (Box 3.1, Folder 22)
  November 12, 1953
- Eastern, Western and Southeastern Carriers' Committees and Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, Volume 9, 1953 (Box 3.1, Folder 23)
  November 13, 1953
- Eastern, Western and Southeastern Carriers' Committees and Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, Volume 27, 1954 (Box 3.1, Folder 24)
  March 16, 1954
- Eastern, Western and Southeastern Carriers' Committees and Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, Brief on Behalf of the Carriers, 1954 (Box 3.1, Folder 25)
  March 5, 1954
- Eastern, Western and Southeastern Carriers' Committees and Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, Volume 25, 1954 (Box 3.1, Folder 26)
  January 18, 1954
- Eastern, Western and Southeastern Carriers' Committees and Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, Volume 5, 1953 (Box 3.1, Folder 27)
  November 9, 1953
- Eastern, Western and Southeastern Carriers' Committees and Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, Volume 1, 1953 (Box 3.1, Folder 28)
  October 27, 1953
- Eastern, Western and Southeastern Carriers' Committees and Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, Brief for the Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, 1954 (Box 3.1, Folder 29)
- Transcript of Proceedings of the Board of Arbitration Between BLF&E and Boston and Maine Railroad. U.S. Board of Mediation, File C-423, Boston, 10/22/39; Transcript of Proceedings of Emergency Board Between BLF&E and Bingham and Garfield Railway (Box 4)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the National Mediation Board. Arbitration Board, Volume 25, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Proceedings of the National Mediation Board. Arbitration Board. Brief on Behalf of the Carriers, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Transcript of the Proceedings of the National Mediation Board. Arbitration Board, Volume 27, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Transcript of the Proceedings of the National Mediation Board. Arbitration Board, Volume 1, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Proceedings of the National Mediation Board. Arbitration Board. Brief for the Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume No. 1, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen vs Bingham and Garfield Railway
  - United States Board of Mediation and Conciliation, 1919 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    In the matter of the arbitration between Chicago & Illinois Midland Railway Company and Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, Order of the Railway Conductors, Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Board of Arbitration. US Board of Mediation, File C-423 [folder 1 of 2], 1929 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    Between Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen v. Boston and Maine Railroad
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Board of Arbitration. US Board of Mediation, File C-423 [folder 2 of 2], 1929 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Special Board of Adjustment, Volume No. 5, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    In the matter of the dispute between: Missouri Pacific Railroad Company and Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, Order of Railway Conductors, Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume No. 10, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume No. 9, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Special Board of Adjustment, Volume No. 7, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume No. 8, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Special Board of Adjustment, Volume No. 6, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume No. 7, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume No. 6, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume No. 5, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume No. 3, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume No. 1 and 2, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume No. 14, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    Between Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen and the Missouri-Pacific Railroad
- Arbitration Pursuant to Agreement dated 3/21/14, of the Controversy Between the BLE and BLF&E and the Georgia and Florida Railway. 1 volume,454 p. Before the Arbitration Board appointed by the National Mediation Board. Carriers Represented by the Eas (Box 5)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume No. 13, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Between the Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen and the Missouri-Pacific Railroad
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume No. 12, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume No. 11, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume No. 10, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume No. 9, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume No. 8, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume No. 7, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume No. 6, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume No. 5, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume No. 4, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume No. 3, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume No. 1, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume No. 2, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Award of Arbitration Board appointed by the National Mediation Board, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    Eastern, Western, and Southeastern Carriers Conference Committees and the Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen (Case A-3391 Arb. 140)
  - Before the Arbitration Board: Brief for the Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Before the Arbitration Board: Brief for the Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Before the Arbitration Board: Brief on Behalf of the Carriers, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Before the Arbitration Board: Brief on behalf of the Carriers Before the Arbitration Board appointed by the National Mediation Board: Case A-3391 Arb. 140 Brief on behalf of the Carriers, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Arbitration of the Controversy between the Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers and Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen and the Georgia and Florida Railway, 1914 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board, Volume No. 1, 1928 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    System Federation No. 103, Railway Employees Department, AFL, Mechanical Section No. 1 vs. New York Central Railroad and Grand Central Terminal (U.S. Board of Mediation File C-351 Arb.)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board, Volume No. 2, 1928 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board, Volume No.13, 1928 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board, Volume No. 14, 1928 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board, Volume No.15, 1928 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board, Volume No. 16, 1928 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board, Volume No.23, 1929 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board, Volume No. 24, 1929 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board, Volume No.25, 1929 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board between Railway Employees Dept., AFL and New York Central Lines. U.S. Board of Mediation C-351 Vol. 1, 2, 13-16, 23-25. 11/28-1/29. (Box 6)
  - Current Rates of Pay, Arbitraries, and Special Allowances for Locomotive Firemen, Helpers, Hostlers and Outside Hostler Helper, 1927 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    Taken from Firemen's Current Pay Schedules, Southeastern Railways; Evolution of a Typical Schedule (Norfolk and Western); Corresponding to Increased Motive Power
  - Excessive Labors of Locomotive Firemen described by Railway Officials and Other Authorities, 1927 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Delayed Promotion. Three Senior Firemen in Service. Three Senior Firemen Furloughed. Railroads in Arbitration, 1927 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Locomotives: Number, Tractive Power, Distribution, 1927 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Southeastern Arbitration 1927; B. L. F. and E.
  - Daily Wage Rates of Locomotive Firemen and Hostlers compared with Daily Wage Rates of Employees in Other Industries 1920 - 1926, 1927 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    Published by Southeastern Arbitration, 1927; B. L. F. and E.
  - Decreasing Wage of Firemen considering: a) Increased cost of living. b) Increased standard of living. c) Increased labor and productivity., 1927 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Operating Statistics Roads in Arbitration 1921 through 1926, 1927 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Purchasing Power of a Fireman's Wage, 1927; Southern District (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Occupational Hazard of Locomotive Firemen, 1927 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Operating Statistics Southern District: 1911 through 1925, 1927 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Compensation of Locomotive Firemen and Other Costs of Locomotive Operation, 1925; Railroads in Arbitration, 1927 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Rates of Locomotive Firemen: Southeastern Railroads, Exhibit No. 13, 1927 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Rates of Locomotive Firemen: Southeastern Railroads, Exhibit No. 14, 1927 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Rates of Locomotive Firemen: Southeastern Railroads, Exhibit No. 15, 1927 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Statement Showing Progress of Stoker Fired Engine Development on the Louisville and Nashville Railroad, 1917-1927 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    Exhibit 14-A
  - All Road and Yard Service, 1927 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    Exhibit 15
  - Passenger Service: Southeastern Railroads, 1927 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    Exhibit 16
  - Statement Showing Tractive Power of Locomotives in Freight Service: Years 1917, 1923, and 1926, 1917-1926 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    Exhibit 17- A
  - Freight Service: Southeastern Railroads, 1927 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    Exhibit 17
  - 1923 Earnings of Conductors and Firemen Compared (Railroad Labor Report No. 5, April 1926) (Box 6, Folder 20)
    Exhibit 21
  - Statement Showing Number of Locomotives and Number Equipped with Stokers at Close of Years 1923, 1924, 1925, and 1926, 1923-1926 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    Exhibit 20
  - Capital Expenditures: Southeastern Railroads, 1927 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    Exhibit 19
  - Traffic Commodities: Southeastern Railroads, 1927 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    Exhibit 18
  - Prosperity, National Income, Average Income: A Study Based on the Estimates of National Bureau of Economic Research, published Feb. 11, 1927 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    Exhibit 22
  - Witnesses (DBR), 1927 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Present Rates of Pay and Proposed Rates for Firemen, Helpers, Hostlers and Outside Hostler Helpers on Southeastern Railroads, 1927 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Excessive Labors of Locomotive Firemen described by Railway Officials and Other Authorities, 1927 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Operating Statistics: Roads in Arbitration, 1921-1926 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Purchasing Power of A Fireman's Wage; Southern District, 1927 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Occupational Hazard of Locomotive Firemen, 1927 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Compensation of Locomotive Firemen and Other Costs of Locomotive Operation (1925): Railroads in Arbitration, 1927 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Operating Statistics. Southern District, 1911 through 1925, 1911-1925 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Daily Wage Rates of Locomotive Firemen and Hostlers compared with Daily Wage Rates of Employees in Other Industries (1920 through 1926), 1920-1926 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Decreasing Wage of Firemen considering: a) Increased cost of living b) Increased standard of living c) Increased labor and productivity, 1927 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Delayed Promotion: Three Senior Firemen in Service, Three Senior Firemen Furloughed; Railroads in Arbitration, 1927 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Locomotives: Number, Tractive Power, Distribution, 1927 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    Published by Southeastern Arbitration 1927; B. L. F. and E.
  - Current Rates of Pay, Arbitraries, and Special Allowances for Locomotive Firemen, Helpers, Hostlers and Outside Hostler Helpers taken from Firemen's Current Pay Schedules; Southeastern Railways, 1927 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    Evolution of a Typical Schedule (Norfolk and Western); Corresponding to Increased Motive Power
  - Present Rates of Pay and Proposed Rates for Firemen, Helpers, Hostlers and Outside Hostler Helpers on Southeastern Railroads; 1927 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Educating and Training Locomotive Fireman: As Advocated by Railway Officials and Other Mechanical Authorities, 1927 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Rates of Locomotive Firemen: Southeastern Railroads, 1927 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Prosperity, National Income, Average Income: A Study Based on the Estimates of National Bureau of Economic Research, published Feb. 11, 1927 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - 1923 Earnings of Conductors and Firemen compared to Railroad Labor Report No. 5; April 1926 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Statement Showing Number of Locomotives and Number Equipped with Stokers at Close of Years 1923, 1924, 1925, 1926, 1923-1926 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Statement showing Number of Locomotives and Number Equipped with Stokers at Close of Years 1923, 1924, 1925, 1926, 1923-1926 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Passenger Service: Southeastern Railroads, 1927 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Earnings of Locomotive Firemen: Southeastern Railroads, 1927 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Locomotives: Southeastern Railroads, 1927 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Traffic Commodities: Southeastern Railroads, 1927 (Box 6, Folder 48)